// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When did we begin talking?",
    answer: "January 8th, 2021",
    options: [
      "January 1st, 2021",
      "january 14th, 2021",
      "January 8th, 2021",
      "January 1st, 2022"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Through which social media app did we meet?",
    answer: "Snapchat",
    options: [
      "Snapchat",
      "Telegram",
      "Instagram",
      "Twitter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many years will our friendship celebrate in our next anniversary?",
    answer: "3 years",
    options: [
      "1 year",
      "2 years",
      "3 years",
      "4 years"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "where is the creator of this page from?",
    answer: "Colombia",
    options: [
      "Mexico",
      "Columbia, SC, US",
      "Colombia",
      "Ecuador"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is your dear friend(Me :>)'s name?",
    answer: "Maria Antonia",
    options: [
      "Marie Antonia",
      "Marian Antonia",
      "María Antonia",
      "Maria Antonia"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the region Antonia is from known for?",
    answer: "Coffee harvest",
    options: [
      "Plantain harvest",
      "Rivers",
      "Coffee harvest",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who is the babiest baby to ever baby?",
    answer: "Ray",
    options: [
      "Blub",
      "Lee May",
      "Otto",
      "Ray"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is Antonia's favorite game series?",
    answer: "Fire Emblem",
    options: [
      "Mario bros",
      "The Sims",
      "Fire Emblem",
      "The legend of Zelda"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of Antonia's close friend?",
    answer: "Jerónimo",
    options: [
      "Mario Antonio",
      "Santiago",
      "Juan Manuel",
      "Jerónimo"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What coding language did the creator of this page's first learn?",
    answer: "Python",
    options: [
      "Python",
      "Java",
      "JavaScript",
      "HTML"
    ]
  },
];

